<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Jorna</title>
    <link>https://davidjorna.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David Jorna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:45:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davidjorna.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://davidjorna.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:45:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidjorna.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m David Jorna. I plan to use this site to share my ideas, programming projects, and technical knowledge, in the hope that someone finds it to be helpful. Conventional wisdom says that you should keep your blog topics focused on a niche in order to gain traction, but I will likely cover a variety of topics. Some of my interests include artificial intelligence, computer vision, education, philosophy, science, and technology, so you can expect content along those lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrain Generation</title>
      <link>https://davidjorna.com/posts/terrain_generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:45:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidjorna.com/posts/terrain_generation/</guid>
      <description>Title: Procedural Terrain Generation Date: 2019-05-14 9:32 Modified: 2019-06-14 21:00 Category: Open Source Projects Tags: Game Development, Projects, Terrain Generation Slug: Terrain1 Authors: David Jorna Summary: Generate a 2D heightmap for use in 3D games and simulations. Featured_Image: /images/thermal_erosion_eroded.png
Motivation Procedural terrain generation encompasses a broad range of techniques, with the goal of efficiently creating a realistic simulated environment. Some of the most famous applications of procedural terrain generation are in Minecraft, which procedurally generated biomes to simulate different climages, and No Man&amp;rsquo;s Sky, which uses procedural techniques to generate entire worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is intranet?</title>
      <link>https://davidjorna.com/posts/what_is_an_intranet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:45:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidjorna.com/posts/what_is_an_intranet/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This post is sponsored by MyHub Intranet Solutions, an affiliate of Daikon Media, who were kind enough to review my indie game. However, this post is meant to be educational and objective; this post is not an advertisement, and I was not censored in any way.
Intranet vs Internet You&amp;rsquo;re might be familiar with something called &amp;ldquo;the internet.&amp;rdquo; It surrounds us and penetrates us. It binds the galaxy together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Publish Your Unity Game to the App Store Without a Mac or an iPhone</title>
      <link>https://davidjorna.com/posts/publish_to_app_store_without_mac/publish-to-app-store-without-a-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidjorna.com/posts/publish_to_app_store_without_mac/publish-to-app-store-without-a-mac/</guid>
      <description>I recently released the beta of my first mobile game, Juggl, for both Android an iOS. Not owning any Apple products besides an old iPod Nano, I found publishing to the App Store to be more difficult than I expected. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder some indie devs neglect the App Store altogether to save themselves the headache of getting through Apple&amp;rsquo;s strict hardware requirements.
This is unfortunate, because they&amp;rsquo;re missing out on a lot of potential revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>